{
    "id": "b63ec576cf864dfcb01cc9a3c4c19518",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was deaf ………………………………. our pleas for help.",
            "description": "Deaf is followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "17391dcf1c4e4cd48506b6c63b8ad2dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Physical activity is beneficial …………………………… health.",
            "description": "We say beneficial to something or somebody.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "774979a5ea0644a4804cb1f81cbb47b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you conscious ……………………………….. your rights and responsibilities?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "about",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f91e2ec6021944feb1ceb2935a2a831b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She refused to comply …………………………………. my request.",
            "description": "We say comply with.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f9e20f18cb364fbcae38300c54e6cf78"
        },
        {
            "question": "The honor was conferred ………………………………. him at the convocation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "254e4dd42e8a457dab42e0d4036a5ecb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He congratulated me ………………………………. my new job.",
            "description": "Congratulate can be followed by on or for.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c0ab38ef3d274439af2a1af79bf1d997"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is thoroughly conversant ……………………………… the problem.",
            "description": "Conversant is followed by with.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7e68b4248dbd4da09d07fe905cd4d761"
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager called ………………………………… an explanation from the cashier.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8a49157e57644475a35d1792c8a76ba2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t care ……………………………… your opinion. If I want to do something, I will do it.",
            "description": "To care about something is to think that it is important. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "about",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04832f63f45748578d3e75fa27fab9f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He fell …………………………….. suspicion.",
            "description": "When you fall under something, you become affected by it. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "under",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "82a57a5a6f87412a8dceeb72efdcf202"
        },
        {
            "question": "The inspector has promised to inquire …………………………………. the complaint.",
            "description": "To inquire into is the look into or probe.",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "about",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20c8210afc034ba1b9d3951e27b2f6d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He inquired …………………………….. homes for sale.",
            "description": "To inquire about is to ask about.",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "about",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75a194263afd4743803ac461cb41638d"
        }
    ]
}